{
    "list_questions": [
        {
            "id": 0,
            "question": "What region is Lille located in?",
            "options": [
                "Normandy",
                "Brittany",
                "Hauts-de-France",
                "Auvergne-Rhône-Alpes"
            ],
            "answer": 2
        },
        {
            "id": 1,
            "question": "Lille is known for its annual event that takes place in September. What is it called?",
            "options": [
                "Bastille Day",
                "Carnival of Nice",
                "Fête de la Musique",
                "Braderie de Lille"
            ],
            "answer": 3
        },
        {
            "id": 2,
            "question": "Which famous art museum can be found in Lille?",
            "options": [
                "The Louvre",
                "Musée d'Orsay",
                "Musée du Quai Branly",
                "Palais des Beaux-Arts"
            ],
            "answer": 3
        },
        {
            "id": 3,
            "question": "Lille is close to the border of which other country?",
            "options": [
                "Germany",
                "Belgium",
                "Switzerland",
                "Italy"
            ],
            "answer": 1
        },
        {
            "id": 4,
            "question": "Which of these is a traditional dish from Lille?",
            "options": [
                "Coq au Vin",
                "Cassoulet",
                "Potjevleesch",
                "Bouillabaisse"
            ],
            "answer": 2
        },
        {
            "id": 5,
            "question": "Lille is famous for its historic central square. What is it called?",
            "options": [
                "Place de la Bastille",
                "Place de la Concorde",
                "Grand Place",
                "Place de la République"
            ],
            "answer": 2
        },
        {
            "id": 6,
            "question": "Which mode of transport is a symbol of Lille and can be seen throughout the city?",
            "options": [
                "Gondolas",
                "Bicycles",
                "Tuk-tuks",
                "Trams"
            ],
            "answer": 3
        },
        {
            "id": 7,
            "question": "Lille hosted matches during which international football tournament?",
            "options": [
                "FIFA World Cup",
                "UEFA European Championship (Euro)",
                "Copa America",
                "AFC Asian Cup"
            ],
            "answer": 1
        },
        {
            "id": 8,
            "question": "The University of Lille is known for its research and contributions to which field?",
            "options": [
                "Medicine",
                "Engineering",
                "Computer Science",
                "Marine Biology"
            ],
            "answer": 0
        },
        {
            "id": 9,
            "question": "What is the local language spoken in Lille, along with French?",
            "options": [
                "Breton",
                "Occitan",
                "Flemish",
                "Corsican"
            ],
            "answer": 2
        }
    ]
}